numbertank.com 2012-09-02

# Numbertank

Privacy Policy

Numbertank.com respects the privacy of users and is committed to protect their privacy in all respects. Should you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at [privacy@numbertank.com](mailto:privacy@numbertank.com).   
This Privacy Policy of Numbertank is to inform users of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of this website, located at [www.numbertank.com](http://www.numbertank.com/) or collected through our presence on other social networking communities, including via SMS and Emails. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any material changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes.   
By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information in India as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing" means using cookies on a computer or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in India. If you reside outside India, your personally identifiable information will be transferred to India, and processed and stored there. By visiting our Site and providing information to us, you consent to such transfer to, and processing in, India.   
If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our use of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [privacy@numbertank.com](mailto:privacy@numbertank.com).   
  
Information Collection and Use   
Our primary goals is to collect personally identifiable information and to provide you with the product and services made available through the Site, including, but not limited, to the Service, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one.   
\- Information Collected Upon Registration.    If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site, you will be required to become a registered user, and to submit certain personally identifiable information to Numbertank. Personally identifiable information that we may collect in such instances may include, full user name, password, email address, city, time zone, telephone number, and other such information.   
\- Additional Information    Your full user name and your photo, if you decide to upload one, are displayed to people in the Numbertank network to enable you to connect with people on Numbertank, as specified in your privacy settings. Once a member, you may provide additional information in the profile section, including but not limited to your bio, as well as your location. You will receive notifications on your cellular phone account in a number of cases, such as when you have a friend whose birthday is next in your contact list. If you contact us by email through the Site, we may keep a record of your contact information and correspondence, and may use your email address, and any information that you provide to us in your message, to respond to you.   
\- Use of Contact Information    In addition, we may use your contact information to market to you, and provide you with information about, our products and services, including but not limited to our Service.   
\- Log Data    When you visit the Site, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit the website. For most users accessing the Internet from an Internet service provider the IP address will be different every time you log on. We do not associate your IP address with any other personally identifiable information to identify you personally, except in case of violation of the "Terms of Service"   
  
Cookies   
Like many websites, we also use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. Numbertank may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and in turn our services. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.    
Information Sharing and Disclosure   
Service Providers   
We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.

Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement   
Numbertank cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Numbertank or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

Business Transfers   
Numbertank may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including your personally identifiable information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity's planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy.

Changing or Deleting Information   
If you are a registered user of the Site, you may access and update or correct the information you provided to us on the website itself. For further queries you can e-mail us at [privacy@numbertank.com](mailto:privacy@numbertank.com).

Security   
Numbertank is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access. We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored personal data to you via email or conspicuous posting on this Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or; (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system.

Our Policy Towards Children   
The Site is not directed to persons under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@numbertank.com](mailto:privacy@numbertank.com). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files.

Contact Information   
If site users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us [privacy@numbertank.com](mailto:privacy@numbertank.com).

Website Administrator   
Business Name: Numbertank.com   
Postal Address: 816-820, Golden Point, Near Telephone Exchange, Ring Road,   
Surat - 395003.   
Gujarat (India)   
Website URL: [www.numbertank.com](http://www.numbertank.com/)
